<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CryptoParty - Utah</title>
    <description>Party like it&#39;s December 31st, 1983</description>
    <link>http://cryptopartyutah.org/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://cryptopartyutah.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Darknet Changes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve taken advantage of the holiday to migrate our darknet sites.  As part of the process, we rekeyed our i2p eepsite/hidden service.  As a result it is necessary to change our service name to &lt;a href=&quot;http://utah.cryptparty.i2p&quot;&gt;utah.cryptoparty.i2p&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please update your bookmarks/addressbooks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently planning events for next year, and should announce our next event before the end of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://cryptopartyutah.org/announcements/2015/11/26/darknet-changes/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cryptopartyutah.org/announcements/2015/11/26/darknet-changes/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GPG Presentation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am posting links to the slides and practical exercise for those of you who attended the GPG Presentation tonight at the SLC Linux User Group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/slides/IntroductionToGPG.pdf&quot;&gt;Introduction To GPG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/slides/GPG_Practical_Exercise.txt&quot;&gt;Practical Exercise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next up, DEFCON 23!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that we will be organizing another CryptoParty in September.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 15:46:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://cryptopartyutah.org/resources/2015/07/27/gpg-presentaiton/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cryptopartyutah.org/resources/2015/07/27/gpg-presentaiton/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crypto &amp; Privacy at DEF CON 23</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;DEF CON is the world’s largest hacker conference held annually in the first part of August in Las Vegas.  While not technically in Utah, DEF CON is near enough for people in the state to attend.  This year’s conference will be held at Bally’s on the 6th through 9th of August.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DEF CON has several ‘villages’ that focus on specific interests (hardware hacking, lockpicking, etc), among these will be the Crypto &amp;amp; Privacy Village.  Last year, the Crypto and Privacy Village held several presentations, workshops, dicussions, and keysigning parties (think of it as a super crypto party).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a great opportunity to learn how to protect yourself online, and associate with others who are passionate about security and privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information, checkout: &lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptovillage.org&quot;&gt;CryptoVillage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 01:46:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://cryptopartyutah.org/announcement/2015/05/18/crypto-and-privacy-village/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cryptopartyutah.org/announcement/2015/05/18/crypto-and-privacy-village/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Salt Lake CryptoParty</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Utah’s first CryptoParty will be held at the 801Labs hackerspace in Salt Lake City on Saturday, April 25th.  The party will start at 9 AM and go all day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;presentations-include&quot;&gt;Presentations include:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Modern Day Cryptography for the Uninitiated&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Introduction to GPG&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to actually use encrypted phone calls&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Keybase.io&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Introduction to I2P&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Salted Challenge Response Authentication Mechanism&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be a key signing party/social after the presentations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The party is being hosted and sponsored by DC801/801Labs. The hackerspace is located at:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;353 East 200 South Suite #B &lt;br /&gt;
Salt Lake City, UT 84111&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information, please visit the party’s website at: &lt;a href=&quot;https://slcrypto.com&quot;&gt;slcrypto.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to see everyone there!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 01:46:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://cryptopartyutah.org/announcement/2015/04/07/slcryptoparty/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cryptopartyutah.org/announcement/2015/04/07/slcryptoparty/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Setting up a Tor Hidden Service</title>
        <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;why-run-a-hidden-service&quot;&gt;Why run a hidden service?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been said that the printing press taught everyone how to read, and that the Internet taught everyone how to write.  While that is debatable, it is certainly true that these technologies 
have dramatically impacted humanity’s ability to express and comsume ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A common approach to obtaining candid information is to provide a way for people to communicate anonymously.  As Oscar Wilde said, “Man is least himself when he talks in his own person. Give 
him a mask, and he will tell you the truth.”  Tor hidden services provide a means for people to communicate anonymously, and speak with candor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-do-you-need-to-run-a-hidden-service&quot;&gt;What do you need to run a hidden service?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While you can run a hidden service on any computer, and nearly any operating system, it is recommended (for security reasons) to use open source software.  The reason is that open source software
can be audited, and changed by the community that uses it, and is therefore more trustworthy than proprietary software (where they may have be beholden to other groups and interests).
This tutorial describes how to use software provided by the Debian and Tor Projects to create a hidden service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is generally a good idea (for availablity) to place the service on a 
system with a ‘always on’ connection to the Internet.  You should be mindful of any acceptable use policies if you plan on hosting the service with a provider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;step-1-install-tor&quot;&gt;Step 1: Install Tor&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone who has spent even a limited amount of time with debian-based systems are familiar with its software package management system.  Instead of installing Tor from source (which is possible), 
I prefer to use package-management whenever possible (easier to update and maintain).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Tor is available from the default debian project repositories, it is usually not as up to date as from the Tor Project repositories.  So we will first install the Tor Project’s repositories into the Debian package management system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The default repositories are found in the /etc/apt/sources.list file.  You can add the Tor Project’s repository by adding the following line to the file:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;deb     http://deb.torproject.org/torproject.org &amp;lt;DISTRIBUTION&amp;gt; main
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should replace the &lt;DISTRIBUTION&gt; label with the codename for your version of Debian (for example wheezy for Debian 7.x).&lt;/DISTRIBUTION&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The packages are signed using the Tor Project’s GPG Keys.  So we will need to add the key to Apt in order to use the repository.  Use the following commands:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; # gpg --keyserver keys.gnupg.net --recv 886DDD89
 # gpg --export A3C4F0F979CAA22CDBA8F512EE8CBC9E886DDD89 | sudo apt-key add -
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we need to update apt now that we have added the Tor project’s repositories:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; # apt-get update
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the repository updated, we will install a package which makes keepig the Tor project’s signing keys up to date:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; # apt-get install deb.torproject.org-keyring
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally,  we install Tor:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; # apt-get install tor
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should now have the Tor service running on your system.  Time for the next step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;step-2-install-a-web-server&quot;&gt;Step 2: Install a Web Server&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In most cases, a hidden service is just a website accessible through Tor.  As with any other website, we will need a webserver.  Any webserver will do the job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would suggest configuring the webserver to only listen to requests from the local server.  The reason is that this will force all interaction with the server through the Tor network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because there are many different webservers, and several tutorials available, I will not go into any further details on how to configure them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: Your hidden service can be any service commonly available on the Internet (ssh, IRC, etc).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;step-3-configure-the-hidden-service&quot;&gt;Step 3: Configure the Hidden Service&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you have Tor and a webserver installed and running, its time to configure the hidden service.  In order to do this, we will need to reconfigure the tor service;  The tor service is configured
using the /etc/tor/torrc file.  Inside the torrc file there is a section for ‘location-hidden services.’  There will be some example configurations for hidden services (commented out).  They will look
similar to this (uncomment them):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# HiddenServiceDir /var/lib/tor/hidden_service/
# HiddenServicePort 80 127.0.0.1:8080
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HiddenServiceDir directive points to the path where the ‘pivate_key’ and the ‘hostname’ files for the hidden service exist.  The ‘pivate_key’ is a secret which you should protect from disclosure, and
the ‘hostname’ file has the .onion address that people will use to access the hidden service.  Both of theses files will be generated by the tor service. It is important that the ‘debian-tor’ user have 
full permissions to this directory.  I would suggest placing the hidden service directory in ‘/var/lib/tor/’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HiddenServicePort directive identifies the port the service will be accessible on inside the tor network, and the local address and port of the service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After modifying the torrc file, and creating the directory, you will need to restart the tor service in order to make the hidden service active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should now have a working Tor hidden-service (the address for your hidden service can be found in the ‘hostname’ file mentioned above).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;references&quot;&gt;Reference(s):&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/docs/tor-hidden-service.html.en&quot;&gt;Configuring Hidden Services for Tor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2014 01:46:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://cryptopartyutah.org/howto/2014/10/10/setting-up-a-tor-hidden-service/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cryptopartyutah.org/howto/2014/10/10/setting-up-a-tor-hidden-service/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Password Management</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-common-problem&quot;&gt;A Common Problem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For most people, the majority of our online accounts are ‘secured’ through credentials 
that involve some type of username and password combination.  It doesn’t take long for
even the most casual online user to accumulate several accounts.  This places many in a
dilemma between security and convenience.  If you use the same credentials for multiple
accounts, then it is easier to remember and manage, but you are more vulnerable to
having multiple accounts being compromised by a singular security breach.  On the other
hand, if you use different credentials for each account, the risk of forgetting them
can increase to the point of being unusable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, even if you are doing your best to be secure, if a service you use is compromised
your account(s) could be at risk.  While there are some other approaches which help 
mitigate this risk, they are not yet in widespread use and/or are currently inconvenient. 
Untill something better comes along and displaces them we are left to cope with
traditional credential-based account security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;things-you-can-do&quot;&gt;Things You Can Do&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Password length and using mixed characters (such as upper and lower case letters, numbers, 
and special characters) are important in securing your accounts.  Cyber criminals 
use dictionary and brute force attacks to compromise accounts.  Using uncommon, long 
passwords can go a long way to frustrate their efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making sure that your account credentials are sent using encryption is also important.
If you send your credentials over an unencrypted connection, anyone in a position
to view the traffic could obtain your credentials.  Make sure that sites
you login are protected using SSL.  As a rule, avoid sharing anything
important on websites that are not secured (Look for a ‘padlock’ icon near the site’s 
address in most popular browsers).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several high-profile services have been breached, and it is only a matter of time
before others experience the same fate.  Protect yourself by using different credentials
for each of your accounts.  This will mitigrate the risk of multiple accounts being 
compromised one service is undermined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;password-managers&quot;&gt;Password Managers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless you have a photographic memory, maintaining a list of all your credentials can
be overwhelming.  Writing them down would help, but then you would run the risks of
losing your list, not having it available when you need it, and/or being compromised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tools exist which can help us protect both our online security and sanity.  These tools 
are known as password managers.  Thses tools can vary from hardware devices to
software applications, from proprietary to open source solutions.  They are usually
secured using a password, or token.  While we may still need to use and remember
a strong password, at least it is only one (not ten or more).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before selecting one, take into consideration your needs.  Do you need it to be 
multiplatform (Windows/MacOS/Linux)?  Do you need it to be available for both
desktop and mobile devices?  How would you create (and store) a backup?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most password managers can auto-generate very strong passwords for you.  Some
can be integrated into your browsers.  Some share common file formats, so that
you can use different managers with the same list file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Implementing good password management can greatly improve your online security.
Password managers can go a long way to make it easier to be more secure online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find one that works for you, and use it.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 15:46:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://cryptopartyutah.org/advice/2014/06/20/password-management/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cryptopartyutah.org/advice/2014/06/20/password-management/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Add SSL to your site</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Part of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://resetthenet.org&quot;&gt;Reset the Net&lt;/a&gt; initative is encouraging webmasters to implement SSL on their sites.  SSL uses
encryption to protect the content of the communications between the visitor and the site.  While using SSL might be ‘optional’ for 
a site that only serves static information (and doesn’t have users submit their personal information), it is irresponsible for sites
that have visitors submit their information.  We will walk people through the steps necessary to protect their 
sites with SSL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;assumptions&quot;&gt;Assumptions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This article assumes that your website is hosted on a server running Linux (We will cover Ubuntu/Debian based systems).  We also assume
that you have admin/root access on your server.  If you are hosted with a service where you don’t have admin/root access, then this 
article will still be useful, but you will probably need to contact your service provider for assistance in some of the steps described 
below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;step-1-generating-your-private-key-and-certificate-signing-request-csr&quot;&gt;Step 1: Generating your Private Key and Certificate Signing Request (CSR)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need a private key (which your server use to communicate securely), and a CSR (which you will use to obtain a certificate).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be using OpenSSL for this step.  There are a number of options (which we will explain) available.  We will start with the following
command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# openssl req -new -newkey rsa:4096 -keyout yourdomain.key -out yourdomain.csr
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explanation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘req -new’ tells openssl that we will be creating a CSR&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘-newkey’ we will also be creating a private key&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘rsa:4096’ the private key will be a RSA key with a keysize of 4096 bits (Note: the minimum keysize currently accepted by certificate authorities is 2048)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘-keyout yourdomain.key’ specify the filename of the private key (Please change ‘yourdomain’ to your domain name)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘-out yourdomain.car’ specify the filename of the CSR (Again change ‘yourdomain’ to your domain name)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are other options that you could use, but this generates an encrypted private key and a CSR.  If you want to generate an unencrypted private key, 
then include ‘-nodes’ after the ‘rsa:4096’ option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OpenSSL will prompt you for a passphase for your key (unless you included the ‘-nodes’ option), and ask you for additional information (some of which is optional).&lt;br /&gt;
Once you finish, you will have a private key and CSR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Debian/Ubuntu, you will generally want to store your private key in the ‘/etc/ssl/private’ directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will use the CSR in the next step to obtain your certificate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;step-2-obtaining-a-certificate&quot;&gt;Step 2: Obtaining a certificate&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A signed certificate is used by a browser to authenticate, and help setup secure communications using SSL/TLS.  A Certificate Authority (CA) is a trusted organization
which is recognized by most browsers to authenticate sites using SSL/TLS.  In order to get a CA to generate a signed certificate you must verify your information, and 
usually pay a fee for their service (Note: there are some ‘free’ certificate authorities).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally, there are three ‘levels’ of verification/validation by CAs:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Domain validation - usually they will send an email message to one of the email addresses associated with the domain name registration.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Organization validation - The CA will investigate your organization to verify its legitimacy (usually more expensive)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Extended validation - Like Organization validation, but even more rigorous (usually done with large organizations and financial institutions)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process will vary, but you will at some point provide the CA with the CSR you generated in Step 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once they have completed validation, the CA will issue a signed certificate for your domain.  Usually they will also include several other certificates asscoiated with
their chain of trust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an alternative, you can ‘self-sign’ and generate your own certificate.  This is simpler and usually cheaper that getting one from a CA, but will most probably 
cause a visitor’s browser to alert and warn of ‘an untrusted site’.  To generate your own certificate, use OpenSSL as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# openssl x509 -req -days 365 -in yourdomain.csr -signkey yourdomain.key -out yourdomain.crt
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explanation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘x509 -req’ tells openssl that we will be creating a signed-certificate&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘-days 365’ our certificate will be valid for one year (most certificates are signed by CAs for the length of period)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘-in yourdomain.csr’ OpenSSL will use the CSR you generated in Step One&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘-signkey yourdomain.key’ OpenSSL will use your private key to ‘sign’ the certificate&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘-out yourdomain.crt’ specify the filename of the certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have your certificate(s) you will generally want to keep them in ‘certs’ directory.  On Debian/Ubuntu systems the ‘certs’ directory is, ‘/etc/ssl/certs’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;step-3-configuring-your-webserver-to-use-ssl&quot;&gt;Step 3: Configuring your webserver to use SSL&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you have your private key and certificate(s), it is time to configure your server to use SSL/TLS.  We will cover configuring Apache (A later article will cover using NGINX).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;configuring-apache-on-debianubuntu&quot;&gt;Configuring Apache on Debian/Ubuntu&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need to enable a few Apache modules in order to use SSL/TLS.  You can enable these modules with the following commands:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# a2enmod ssl
# a2enmod headers
# a2enmod rewrite
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first module is the only one truly necessary to get SSL working, but the other modules will be used in our example configuration, so it is a good idea to add them now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, you will need to create/modify the VirtualHost files located at: ‘/etc/apache2/sites-available’.  By default, there are two files, ‘000-default.conf’ and ‘default-ssl.conf’.&lt;br /&gt;
The ‘000-default.conf’ file is configured to serve http, and the ‘default-ssl.conf’ is configured for SSL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: the ‘default-ssl.conf’ site is not enabled by default. You can enable it with the following command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# a2ensite default-ssl.conf
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many ways to configure SSL, but the example we will show you redirects all http traffic to https (this is why we enabled the ‘rewrite’ Apache module).&lt;br /&gt;
Below is an example (which you can use unmodified) for the ‘000-default.conf’ file:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;VirtualHost *:80&amp;gt;
    ReWriteEngine on
    ReWriteCond %{SERVER_PORT} !^443$
    ReWriteRule ^/(.*) https://%{HTTP_HOST}/$1 [NC,R,L]
&amp;lt;/VirtualHost&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, is the ‘default-ssl.conf’ file (This one is more involved).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;IfModule mod_ssl.c&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;VirtualHost _default_:443&amp;gt;
    ServerName yourdomain
    ServerAlias www.yourdomain

    DocumentRoot /var/www/
    &amp;lt;Directory /&amp;gt;
            Options FollowSymLinks
            AllowOverride None
    &amp;lt;/Directory&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;Directory /var/www/&amp;gt;
            Options FollowSymLinks MultiViews
            AllowOverride None
            Order allow,deny
            allow from all
    &amp;lt;/Directory&amp;gt;

    ErrorLog ${APACHE_LOG_DIR}/error.log

    # Possible values include: debug, info, notice, warn, error, crit,
    # alert, emerg.
    LogLevel warn

    CustomLog ${APACHE_LOG_DIR}/ssl_access.log combined

    # Setup  HTTP Strict Transportation Security
    Header always set Strict-Transport-Security &quot;max-age=63072000; includeSubDomains&quot;

    SSLEngine on

    SSLCertificateFile    /etc/ssl/certs/yourdomain.crt
    SSLCertificateKeyFile /etc/ssl/private/yourdomain.key
    SSLCertificateChainFile /etc/ssl/certs/yourdomain.chain

    SSLProtocol ALL -SSLv2 -SSLv3
    SSLHonorCipherOrder On
    SSLCipherSuite AES256+EECDH:!aNULL

&amp;lt;/VirtualHost&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/IfModule&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key points of interest are the lines which start with ‘SSLCertificate’, you will want to make sure that they are pointing to the files you created/obtained in steps one and two.
The line that starts with ‘Header’ will help prevent visitors to your site from connecting in the future via http, and is a good security move. You will need to modify this 
example to match your domain/website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you are satified the these files, you’ll need to restart Apache to make your changes effective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# service apache2 restart
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: If your private key is encrypted, then you will be prompted for your password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;step-4-test-your-site&quot;&gt;Step 4: Test Your Site&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it is time to verify that your site is working with SSL.  Certainly, visiting the site is a good step, but there is a tool available online with will give your site’s SSL Configuration a thorough testing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ssllabs.com/ssltest&quot;&gt;SSL Labs - SSL Test&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 01:46:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://cryptopartyutah.org/howto/2014/06/05/add-ssl-to-your-site/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cryptopartyutah.org/howto/2014/06/05/add-ssl-to-your-site/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the Party!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On this, the first anniversary of the Snowden revelations, we announce the formation of CryptoParty - Utah.  Many people have become concerned 
about their online privacy, but don’t know what they can do to protect it.  We will be holding an ongoing series of events, where we can learn 
to protect our online privacy through the use of cryptographic tools, and security practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are several tools and resources available to help us, but learning about what’s available, and how to effectively use them can be a 
challenge.  We want to enable people to overcome such challenges so that they can use technology and be in control of their online privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please join and help us.  If you have mastered a technology/tool which would help others protect their online privacy, then please conduct a 
workshop and help others.  There are a number of tools/techniques we have planned to present already, but we are always open to more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our inaugural meeting will be anounced shortly, so please visit us again soon.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 02:03:56 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://cryptopartyutah.org/announcement/2014/06/04/welcome-to-the-party/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://cryptopartyutah.org/announcement/2014/06/04/welcome-to-the-party/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
